

Contact

Telegram @auddax

Email auddax@gmail.com

Linkedin <u>kirillkonovalov</u>

Github auddax

Location Russia, Nizhny Novgorod

Skills

React.js JavaScript **TypeScript** MobX Node.js Git

Language

Russian Native

English Intermediate

Kirill Konovalov

Frontend Software Engineer | React.js, MobX

About me

Highly skilled frontend developer with a passion for both continuous learning and for personal growth. Ready to bring my professional experience and knowledge to the company where I will have the opportunity to apply my skills and improve them.

Experience

2022 - present Gazprombank

Frontend Software Engineer Main responsibilities:

· Development and maintaining the frontend side of current solutions

2020 - 2022 Freelance

Frontend Developer Main responsibilities:

- Building dynamic, interactive frontend applications in React.js and Typescript
- Cross-browser development and testing
- Providing applications performance through JavaScript profiling and code optimization

Projects

Notes Keeper

Google Keep clone note-taking app built using React and Material UI component library

<u>LearnWords</u>

SPA for learning new english words. Built using pure TypeScript without any JS framework

Education

2023 **RS School** Course: React

2022

Course: JavaScript/Front-end

RS School

Bachelor Degree in History

2001 - 2006 Lobachevsky State University of Nizhny Novgorod